https://www.digiscribe.info/privacy-policy/

Home>Privacy Policy
Digiscribe recognizes and values your right to privacy. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.
This Privacy Policy describes Digiscribe’s policies and procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as it pertains to this website (digiscribe.info).
By using this website, you consent to the terms of Digiscribe’s Website Privacy Policy and to Digiscribe’s processing of personal information for the purposes set forth below.
Digiscribe reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you, and Digiscribe will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on this website as soon as they go into effect. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
Index
Information We Collect
How We Use Collected Information
Links to External Websites & Social Media
How You Can Manage Your Information
GDPR Rights
How to Contact Us
1. Information We Collect
Cookies
Digiscribe uses cookies to help us provide better customer service, to enhance the user experience and deliver personalized content. Many improvements and updates to this website are based on the data collected, such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. A “cookie” is a small data file that is written to your computer’s hard drive by your web browser. A cookie file can contain and/or automatically collect information, such as a user identification code or IP address, mobile device ID, time zone setting, location data, language preference, and operating system, platform that a website will use to track the pages and number of times you have visited. The data read from these cookies may be linked to personally identifying (PII) and non-personally identifying (non-PII) information.
If you are covered by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you have the ability to accept or decline cookies from the consent banner that appears at the bottom of every page until you choose your cookie preferences. You may review and change your preferences at any time by accessing the cookie declaration here. However, if you choose to decline cookies, not all features of the website may operate as intended.
If you are not covered by the GDPR, you consent to the use of our cookies if you continue to use our website.
Information You Provide
Digiscribe gathers data that is submitted voluntarily to provide information on our services and products, market promotional programs, provide customer service, and market measurement. We do not collect personal data such as social security numbers. We use the data to monitor Digiscribe website usage, to allow us to assess your needs and improve the Digiscribe website.
Form Submissions
Digiscribe collects data from you through our contact, subscriber, and registration forms where you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information about yourself. Information requested includes contact information such as your name, company name, email address, and phone number.
The information is retained in a secure database and is not rented, sold, or shared with other people or companies except to provide information on the products or services you’ve requested.
Surveys, Polls, & Quizzes
From time-to-time our site requests information from visitors via surveys, polls, and quizzes. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the visitor user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information such as name, company name, email address, and phone number. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our services and this site. Any other survey that deviates from this stated policy will explicitly state this from the survey page.
Blog Comments
Our website offers publicly accessible information including a comment section on our blogs. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. In the event that you choose to post information in this context, it becomes generally available to the public, and we have no ability to control or limit its use by visitors to our site.
Children’s Privacy
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not knowingly collect (nor do we wish to collect) any personally identifiable information or other user information from children under the age of 13. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are less than 13 years old, please do not send any user information to us–including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our database.If you believe we collected information about a child under 13, please see “How to Contact Us” below.
2. How We Use Collected Information
The personal information that is provided to Digiscribe may be stored, processed, and used by Digiscribe for the following purposes:
To provide information about our company, products and/or services, including updates, notifications, and details of any offers or promotions
To improve customer service and technical support
To process event/webinar registration
To assist us in improving our products, services, or the content of this website
For our own internal marketing and research purposes
To analyze information for trends and statistics
We may also provide this information to an agent acting on Digiscribe’s behalf in connection with the activities described above.
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Information Security
To protect the privacy of personal information provided by you, Digiscribe employs industry-standard controls including physical access controls, Internet firewalls, intrusion detection, and network monitoring. Additionally, only authorized administrators and staff have access to systems containing such information.
3. Links to External Websites & Social Media
Outgoing Links
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Digiscribe website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Social Media
Our Websites include social media functionality, such as sharing content to outside social media platforms. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.
4. How You Can Manage Your Information
Verifying Your Information
You may check your information to verify, update, or correct it, and to have any obsolete information removed. You can also ask to review any of the information that we have retained, how we have used it, and to whom we have disclosed it at any time by contacting us as indicated in the “Contacting Us” section below. Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, and provided we can authenticate your identity, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it amended as appropriate. You may also ask us to change your preferences regarding how we use or disclose your information, or let us know that you do not wish to receive any further communication from us.
Opting Out
Visitors who no longer wish to receive blog posts updates or marketing communications may opt out of receiving them. Each email communication has an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message. In addition to unsubscribing, marketing and technical communications have a link to update your email preferences. We will no longer send you any communication you choose to opt out of unless you tell us otherwise.
5. GDPR Rights
The GDPR is a comprehensive EU data privacy law that went into effect on May 25, 2018. This regulation states that everyone in the EU has a right to protection of their personal data, and applies to all companies who collect and process data for EU residents. Rights under the GDPR include:
The right to access the personal data the organization is processing, as well as to receive information about the particulars of the processing activities;
The right of an individual in the EU to have the personal data concerning him or her be corrected or updated;
The “Right to Erasure,” sometimes called the “Right to be Forgotten,” which enables individuals in the EU to require the deletion of their personal data under certain circumstances “without undue delay.” Circumstances that may trigger this right include the data’s retention becoming no longer necessary for the purposes for which the data was collected;
The right to withdraw a previously given consent to the use of personal data;
The “Right to Object” to use of an individual’s personal data for some types of “profiling” or automated decision making. This includes the right to be informed if the data subject’s information will be used for automated decision making or profiling;
The “Right to Portability” in certain circumstances, which includes the right to get a copy of stored personal data an individual has provided and to transfer the data, unimpeded, to another organization;
The right to complain to a local data protection authority in the EU if a data subject believes that his or her data is being unlawfully processed.
6. How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns, including requests regarding GDPR Rights for persons living in the EU, please contact us, preferably via email. You will need to provide your name and email address(es) and proper identification will be required before any action is taken.
Data Controller Contact Information
Digiscribe International
150 Clearbrook Road
Suite 125
Elmsford, NY 10523
info@digiscribe.info
To view our GDPR compliant data processing policy that pertains to our practices as a Data Processor of our clients’ data, click here.
Last updated: 10/8/18
New York
(800) 686-7577
150 Clearbrook Road Suite 125 Elmsford, NY 10523
New England
(877) 550-2088
1400 Providence Highway Suite 3150 Norwood, MA 02062
We'd Love To Hear From You
first*last*co*email*
phone*comments*sourceWebsitesiteNew Yorksource detailsCAPTCHADigiscribe is committed to your privacy. We use the information you provide to us to contact you about our relevant services and products. For more information, see our Privacy Policy.
Site Map
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
GDPR Data Processing Policy
